Society of Southwest Archivists records, Inclusive: 1970-2017, Bulk: 1973-1993, 2003-2016
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- Annual Meeting Materials, 1972-2015, undated; 1
  - 27th Annual Meeting, 1998-1999, undated; 27
    - Literary: Participation Lists: Name Tags (1 of 2), 1999 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Literary: Participation Lists: Name Tags (2 of 2), 1999 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Literary: Participation Lists: Tours, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Literary: Participation Lists: Workshops, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Literary: Program, 1999 May 27-29 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Literary: Promotional Materials, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Photographs (1 of 2), 1999 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Photographs (2 of 2), 1999 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Negatives (1 of 2), 1999 (Box 44 OVZ, Folder 3)
    - Negatives (2 of 2), 1999 (Box 44 OVZ, Folder 4)
  - 28th Annual Meeting, 2000; 28
    General condition: Excellent.
    - Correspondence (1 of 2), 2000 February 15-16 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence (2 of 2), 2000 February 15-16 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Literary: Minutes, 2000 May 20 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Photographs (1 of 4), 2000 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Photographs (2 of 4), 2000 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Photographs (3 of 4), 2000 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Photographs (4 of 4), 2000 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - 29th Annual Meeting, 2000-2002, undated; 29
    - Correspondence, 2000 February (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Correspondence, 2000 May (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Correspondence, 2000 October-2001 February (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Correspondence, 2001 March-May 1 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Correspondence, 2001 May 2-11 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Correspondence, 2001 May 16-21 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Correspondence, 2001 May 22-June 2 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Correspondence, 2001 June 4-2002 (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Correspondence, undated (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Legal, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Financial, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Literary: Business Session, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Literary: Directory of Conference and Workshop Pre-Registrants, 2001 May 24-26 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Literary: Disaster Workshop (1 of 8), 2001 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Literary: Disaster Workshop (2 of 8), 2001 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Literary: Disaster Workshop (3 of 8), 2001 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Literary: Disaster Workshop (4 of 8), 2001 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Literary: Disaster Workshop (5 of 8), 2001 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Literary: Disaster Workshop (6 of 8), 2001 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Literary: Disaster Workshop (7 of 8), 2001 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Literary: Disaster Workshop (8 of 8), 2001 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Literary: General (1 of 2), circa 2001 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Literary: General (2 of 2), circa 2001 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Literary: Notes, circa 2001 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Literary: Participation Lists, 2001 April 26 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Literary: Participation Lists, 2001 April 27 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Literary: Participation Lists, 2001 May 7-18 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Literary: Participation Lists, 2001 May 19 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Literary: Participation Lists, circa 2001 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Literary: Presentation Slides, 2001 May (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Literary: Programs (1 of 3), circa 2001 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Literary: Programs (2 of 3), circa 2001 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Literary: Programs (3 of 3), circa 2001 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Literary: Registration, circa 2001 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Literary: Registration Statistics, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Literary: Reports, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Photographs (1 of 2), 2001 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Photographs (2 of 2), 2001 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Negatives (1 of 2), 2001 (Box 44 OVZ, Folder 5)
    - Negatives (2 of 2), 2001 (Box 44 OVZ, Folder 6)
  - 30th Annual Meeting, 2002; 30
    - Financial, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Literary: Directory of Conference Attendees, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Literary: General, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Literary: Minutes, 2002 May 18 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Literary: Participation Lists (1 of 4), 2002 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Literary: Participation Lists (2 of 4), 2002 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Literary: Participation Lists (3 of 4), 2002 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Literary: Participation Lists (4 of 4), 2002 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Literary: Program, 2002 May 16-19 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - 31st Annual Meeting, 2003; 31
    - Correspondence and Literary: Mark Lambert, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - Literary: General, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - Literary: Minutes, 2003 May 24 (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Literary: Program, 2003 May 22-24 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Photographs (1 of 5), 2003 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Photographs (2 of 5), 2003 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Photographs (3 of 5), 2003 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Photographs (4 of 5), 2003 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Photographs (5 of 5), 2003 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - 32nd Annual Meeting, 2004; 32
    - Literary: Minutes, 2004 May 29 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Literary: Program, 2004 May 27-29 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Literary: Registration Packet, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Literary: Roster of Attendees, 2004 May 17 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Photographs (1 of 2), 2004 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Photographs (2 of 2), 2004 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Negatives (1 of 2), 2004 (Box 44 OVZ, Folder 7)
    - Negatives (2 of 2), 2004 (Box 44 OVZ, Folder 8)
  - 33rd Annual Meeting, 2005; 33
    - Literary: General, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Literary: Program, 2005 May 26-28 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Photographs: Board Meeting and Old State House Reception (1 of 2), 2005 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Photographs: Board Meeting and Old State House Reception (2 of 2), 2005 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Photographs: Boutin's Dinner and Port Hudson Tour (1 of 2), 2005 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Photographs: Boutin's Dinner and Port Hudson Tour (2 of 2), 2005 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Photographs: Breakfast and Rural Life Museum Dinner (1 of 2), 2005 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Photographs: Breakfast and Rural Life Museum Dinner (2 of 2), 2005 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Negatives: Board Meeting and Old State House Reception (1 of 2), 2005 (Box 44 OVZ, Folder 9)
    - Negatives: Board Meeting and Old State House Reception (2 of 2), 2005 (Box 44 OVZ, Folder 10)
    - Negatives: Breakfast and Rural Life Museum Dinner (1 of 2), 2005 (Box 44 OVZ, Folder 11)
    - Negatives: Breakfast and Rural Life Museum Dinner (2 of 2), 2005 (Box 44 OVZ, Folder 12)
    - Negatives: Boutin's Dinner and Port Hudson Tour (1 of 2), 2005 (Box 44 OVZ, Folder 13)
    - Negatives: Boutin's Dinner and Port Hudson Tour (2 of 2), 2005 (Box 44 OVZ, Folder 14)
  - 34th Annual Meeting, 2006; 34
    - Literary: Minutes, 2006 May 27 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Literary: Program, 2006 May 25-27 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Literary: Registration Packet, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - 35th Annual Meeting, 2007; 35
    - Literary: General, 2007 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Literary: Minutes, 2007 June 2 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Literary: Program, 2007 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Literary: Registration and Rosters, 2007 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Photographic, circa 2007 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - 36th Annual Meeting, 2008; 36
    - Literary: Program, 2008 May 21-24 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - 37th Annual Meeting, 2009; 37
    - Literary: Minutes, 2009 May 23 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - 38th Annual Meeting, 2009-2010; 38
    - Literary: Minutes, Notes, and Presentation Materials, 2009-2010 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Literary: Program, 2010 April 28-May 1 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - 40th Annual Meeting, 2012; 40
    - Literary: Program, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Flash Drive: PowerPoint Slides, 2012 (Box 45 OVZ, Folder 5)
  - 41st Annual Meeting, 2013; 41
    - Literary: Program, 2013 May 22-25 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - 42nd Annual Meeting, 2014; 42
    - Literary: Program, 2014 May 28-31 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - 43rd Annual Meeting, 2015; 43
    - Literary: General, 2015 (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Literary: Guide, 2015 (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Literary: Program, 2015 May 20-23 (Box 9, Folder 38)
- Committee Documents, 1972-2017, undated; 2
  This series contains materials organized by committee, including correspondence, various financial and literary documents, and a few photographs. Some manuscripts in this series are closely related to specific annual meetings, such as the Site Selection Committee and the Local Arrangements Committee. The Executive Board correspondence filed as “Leon Miller” was kept together because it was numbered consecutively, even though Miller had served on many committees. Overall, the series is in excellent condition.
  Cassette tape; Compact disk (CD); Floppy disk
  - Executive Board, 1973-2017, undated; 1
    - Correspondence, 1973-1974 July (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1974 August-September (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1974 October-1975 April 7 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1975 April 14-August (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1975 September-October (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1975 December 1 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1976 January-February (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1976 April-May (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1976 June-July (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1976 August-September 17 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1976 September 20-December (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1977 January-April (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1977 May-July (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, 1977 August (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, 1977 September-October (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, 1977 November-1978 January (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, 1978 February (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, 1978 March-May 15 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, 1978 May 18-31 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, 1978 June 9-15 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, 1978 June 5-16 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, 1978 June 29-August (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence, 1978 September 15-26 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence, 1978 September 27-November 10 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence, 1978 November 16 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence, 1978 November 27-1979 January 15 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence, 1979 January 16-23 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence, 1979 January 26-March 6 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence, 1979 March 9-April 10 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence, 1979 April 11-30 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence, 1979 May (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Correspondence, 1979 June-August (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Correspondence, 1979 September-October (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Correspondence, 1979 November-1980 January 10 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Correspondence, 1980 January 17-April 11 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Correspondence, 1980 April 15-June 17 (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Correspondence, 1980 June 20-December (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Correspondence, 1981 April-August (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Correspondence, 1981 September-1982 February (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Correspondence, 1982 April-1984 May (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Correspondence, 1984 June-October 3 (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - Correspondence, 1984 October 10-November (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - Correspondence, 1984 December-1985 April 25 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1985 April 29-1987 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1988 January-May 25 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1988 May (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1988 June (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1988 July-August 24 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1988 August 30 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1988 September-October (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1988 November (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1988 December (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1989 January-February (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1989 March (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1989 April 3-7 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, 1989 April 10-13 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, 1989 April 20-May (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence (1 of 2), 1989 May 8-9 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence (2 of 2), 1989 May 8-9 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, 1989 May 10-31 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence (1 of 2), 1989 June-July (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence (2 of 2), 1989 June-July (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, 1989 August 1-16 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, 1989 August 21-30 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence (1 of 2), 1989 September-October (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence (2 of 2), 1989 September-October (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence, 1989 November-December (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence, 1990 February-May 21 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence, 1990 May 22-August 13 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence, 1990 August 27-November (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence, 1991 January-March 6 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence, 1991 March 7-14 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence, 1991 March 15-20 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Correspondence, 1991 March 21-May (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Correspondence, 1991 June-September (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Correspondence, 1991 October —December (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Correspondence, 1992 January-March (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Correspondence, 1992 May-June 12 (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - Correspondence, 1992 June 16-July (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - Correspondence, 1992 August-December (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - Correspondence (1 of 2), 1993 January-April (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - Correspondence (2 of 2), 1993 January-April (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - Correspondence, 1993 May-December (Box 11, Folder 41)
    - Correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 11, Folder 42)
    - Correspondence, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 43)
    - Correspondence, 1997-1998 September (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1998 October-1999 May (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1999 June-July 2 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1999 July 6-December (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 2000-2003 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence (1 of 3), undated (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence (2 of 3), undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence (3 of 3), undated (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence: Leon Miller (1 of 28), 1998-2001 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence: Leon Miller (2 of 28), 1998-2001 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence: Leon Miller (3 of 28), 1998-2001 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence: Leon Miller (4 of 28), 1998-2001 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence: Leon Miller (5 of 28), 1998-2001 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence: Leon Miller (6 of 28), 1998-2001 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence: Leon Miller (7 of 28), 1998-2001 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence: Leon Miller (8 of 28), 1998-2001 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence: Leon Miller (9 of 28), 1998-2001 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence: Leon Miller (10 of 28), 1998-2001 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence: Leon Miller (11 of 28), 1998-2001 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence: Leon Miller (12 of 28), 1998-2001 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence: Leon Miller (13 of 28), 1998-2001 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence: Leon Miller (14 of 28), 1998-2001 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence: Leon Miller (15 of 28), 1998-2001 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence: Leon Miller (16 of 28), 1998-2001 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence: Leon Miller (17 of 28), 1998-2001 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence: Leon Miller (18 of 28), 1998-2001 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence: Leon Miller (19 of 28), 1998-2001 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence: Leon Miller (20 of 28), 1998-2001 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence: Leon Miller (21 of 28), 1998-2001 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence: Leon Miller (22 of 28), 1998-2001 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence: Leon Miller (23 of 28), 1998-2001 (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Correspondence: Leon Miller (24 of 28), 1998-2001 (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - Correspondence: Leon Miller (25 of 28), 1998-2001 (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - Correspondence: Leon Miller (26 of 28), 1998-2001 (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - Correspondence: Leon Miller (27 of 28), 1998-2001 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - Correspondence: Leon Miller (28 of 28), 1998-2001 (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - Correspondence: TSHA Program, 1989-1992 January (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - Correspondence: TSHA Program, 1992 February-April (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - Correspondence: TSHA Program, 1992 May-October (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - Correspondence: TSHA Program, 1992 December (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - Financial: Budget, 1976-1980 (Box 12, Folder 41)
    - Financial: Budget, 1983-1988 (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - Financial: Budget, 1989-2003 (Box 12, Folder 43)
    - Financial: General, 1975-1987 (Box 12, Folder 44)
    - Legal: Articles of Incorporation, 1972-1976 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Legal: Articles of Incorporation, 1978, undated (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Legal: Articles of Incorporation, undated (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Legal: Bills, circa 1993 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Legal: Resolutions, 1974, undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Literary: Agendas and Reports, 1981-1985 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Literary: Agendas and Reports, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Literary: Committee Charges (1 of 3), undated (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Literary: Committee Charges (2 of 3), undated (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Literary: Committee Charges (3 of 3), undated (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Literary: Essay: TSHA Program, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Literary: Essay: TSHA Program, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Literary: Essay: TSHA Program, undated (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Literary: General (1 of 2), 1978-1991 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Literary: General (2 of 2), 1978-1991 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Literary: General (1 of 2), undated (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Literary: General (2 of 2), undated (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Literary: General: TSHA Program, 1992, undated (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Literary: Minutes, 1972-1973 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Literary: Minutes, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Literary: Minutes, 1975 February 21 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Literary: Minutes, 1975 May 1 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Literary: Minutes, 1975 May 3-September (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Literary: Minutes (1 of 2), 1976 January 30 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Literary: Minutes (2 of 2), 1976 January 30 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Literary: Minutes (1 of 2), 1976 May 5-7 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Literary: Minutes (2 of 2), 1976 May 5-7 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Literary: Minutes, 1976 September (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Literary: Minutes, 1977 January (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Literary: Minutes, 1977 May (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Literary: Minutes (1 of 2), 1977 September 23 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Literary: Minutes (2 of 2), 1977 September 23 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Literary: Minutes, 1977 October-1978 January (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - Literary: Minutes, 1978 May (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - Literary: Minutes, 1978 September (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - Literary: Minutes (1 of 2), 1979 (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - Literary: Minutes (2 of 2), 1979 (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - Literary: Minutes (1 of 2), 1979 (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - Literary: Minutes (2 of 2), 1979 (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - Literary: Minutes (1 of 2), 1980 May (Box 13, Folder 40)
    - Literary: Minutes (2 of 2), 1980 May (Box 13, Folder 41)
    - Literary: Minutes (1 of 2), 1980 November 14 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Literary: Minutes (2 of 2), 1980 November 14 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Literary: Minutes (1 of 2), 1980 December 12 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Literary: Minutes (2 of 2), 1980 December 12 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Literary: Minutes (1 of 2), 1981 May 6 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Literary: Minutes (2 of 2), 1981 May 6 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Literary: Minutes (1 of 2), 1981 May 8 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Literary: Minutes (2 of 2), 1981 May 8 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Literary: Minutes (1 of 3), 1981 September (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Literary: Minutes (2 of 3), 1981 September (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Literary: Minutes (3 of 3), 1981 September (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Literary: Minutes: Notes, 1981 September (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Literary: Minutes (1 of 2), 1982 January (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Literary: Minutes (2 of 2), 1982 January (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Literary: Minutes (1 of 2), 1982 May 12 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Literary: Minutes (2 of 2), 1982 May 12 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Literary: Minutes, 1982 May 13-September (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Literary: Minutes (1 of 2), 1982 December (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Literary: Minutes (2 of 2), 1982 December (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Literary: Minutes (1 of 2), 1983 May 4-6 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Literary: Minutes (2 of 2), 1983 May 4-6 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Literary: Minutes, 1983 September (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Literary: Minutes, 1983 December (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Literary: Minutes, 1984 May 16 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Literary: Minutes (1 of 2), 1984 May 18-September (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Literary: Minutes (2 of 2), 1984 May 18-September (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Literary: Minutes (1 of 2), 1984 December (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Literary: Minutes (2 of 2), 1984 December (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Literary: Minutes (1 of 2), 1985 May 8 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Literary: Minutes (2 of 2), 1985 May 8 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Literary: Minutes, 1985 May 10 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Literary: Minutes (1 of 2), 1985 November (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Literary: Minutes (2 of 2), 1985 November (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - Literary: Minutes (1 of 2), 1986 January (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - Literary: Minutes (2 of 2), 1986 January (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - Literary: Minutes, 1986 May 21 (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - Literary: Minutes, 1986 May 23-December (Box 14, Folder 37)
    - Literary: Minutes, 1987 May 20 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    - Literary: Minutes, 1987 May 22 (Box 14, Folder 39)
    - Literary: Minutes (1 of 2), 1987 November (Box 14, Folder 40)
    - Literary: Minutes (2 of 2), 1987 November (Box 14, Folder 41)
    - Literary: Minutes (1 of 2), 1988 May (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Literary: Minutes (2 of 2), 1988 May (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Literary: Minutes, 1988 November (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Literary: Minutes (1 of 5), 1989 May 17-18 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Literary: Minutes (2 of 5), 1989 May 17-18 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Literary: Minutes (3 of 5), 1989 May 17-18 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Literary: Minutes (4 of 5), 1989 May 17-18 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Literary: Minutes (5 of 5), 1989 May 17-18 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Literary: Minutes (1 of 4), 1989 November (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Literary: Minutes (2 of 4), 1989 November (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Literary: Minutes (3 of 4), 1989 November (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Literary: Minutes (4 of 4), 1989 November (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Literary: Minutes (1 of 2), 1990 May 16 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Literary: Minutes (2 of 2), 1990 May 16 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Literary: Minutes, 1990 May 18 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Literary: Minutes (1 of 2), 1990 September (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Literary: Minutes (2 of 2), 1990 September (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Literary: Minutes (1 of 2), 1991 January (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Literary: Minutes (2 of 2), 1991 January (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Literary: Minutes (1 of 3), 1991 May (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Literary: Minutes (2 of 3), 1991 May (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Literary: Minutes (3 of 3), 1991 May (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Literary: Minutes (1 of 2), 1991 October (Box 15, Folder 23)